huggies.co.in 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy - Huggies India | Pregnancy & Baby Care Tips

**Introduction**

Kimberly-Clark India (Kimberly-Clark India) is an affiliate of Kimberly-Clark Corporation ("Kimberly-Clark"), hereinafter collectively known as “We” or “Our”. Kimberly-Clark and all its affiliates respects and upholds your rights to privacy protection in respect of the collection, use, disclosure and handling of personal information. This Policy details the practices we have adopted to protect your privacy, so that you can feel confident about how we manage the personal information you entrust to us. 

**When and how do we collect personal information?**

Personal information is any information that can be used to identify you. We may collect information from you including your personal information (such as name, e-mail, phone number, date of birth and postal address) in the following ways: 

  1. through our websites; 
  2. when you contact our Consumer Advisory Service in order to make a consumer inquiry or complaint about a particular Kimberly-Clark product; 
  3. when you participate in Kimberly-Clark or its affiliates’s consumer promotions and market research; and 

**What do we do with the personal information?**

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to ensure that our consumers are satisfied with our products and to provide our consumers with the best possible quality of customer service. Your personal information is never shared, sold, rented or otherwise disclosed outside the company (except as required for any statutory or legal requirements) in ways different from what is described in this Privacy Policy. We will take all reasonable steps to maintain the security and integrity of your personal information including the use of computer access passwords, lock-up cabinets, personnel policies and firewalls. 

**Information collected through our websites**

We do not collect personally-identifiable information from you, unless you provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means you are under no obligation to provide personal information when visiting our websites. However, if you specifically agree to follow-up contacts by us or ask to be put on our mailing list, we may require your personal information in order to contact you from time to time. 

There are some features of our websites that require you to sign up to use. If you do sign up, we use the information you supply for the purpose of providing products, product information or services you request. Because of the volume of requests we receive, we may have to give your name, e-mail and postal addresses to a fulfillment house or distributor of our products who assist us in carrying out your requests. 

Our websites sometimes include notices of sweepstakes or other promotions we are conducting, and we may permit you to enter electronically in some cases. If that occurs, we will use the information in accordance with the section below entitled "Consumer Promotions and Market Research". 

**Children**

Children's Privacy is of primary concern to us. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. Any communication we receive that is identified as being from a child under the age of 13 will not be kept by Kimberly-Clark. 

**Cookies**

Like many companies, we sometimes use "cookie" technology on our websites. These cookies are stored on your computer by your browser. When you log in, the cookie tells us whether you've visited us before or you are a new visitor. The cookie doesn't obtain any personal information about you or provide us with any way to contact you and the cookie doesn't extract any information from your computer. We use the cookie to help us identify website features in which you have the greatest interest, so that we can provide more of what you want. 

**Links**

Websites operated by Kimberly-Clark may contain links to other sites operated by third parties. Kimberly-Clark makes no representations or warranties as to the privacy practices of any third-party site and is not responsible for the Privacy Policies of other sites. 

**Information collected through consumer advisory service**

Kimberly-Clark will use the details you provide to our Consumer Advisory Service (whether by e-mail, telephone, letter or fax) in order to provide you with the information, services and products necessary to satisfy your consumer inquiry or complaint. This may involve sending a replacement product, information sheet or follow-up letter in relation to your inquiry or complaint or making a follow-up call. We may also use the information you provide to monitor repeat complaints about a particular Kimberly-Clark product. 

Personal information collected from you by our Consumer Advisory Service may also be used for internal product development and quality control purposes. 

Your personal data is stored in a database and we also keep paper records of all correspondence that is sent to you. Any serious complaints that Kimberly-Clark receives are printed out and filed separately in hard copy so that they may be given special attention and be investigated expediently. 

If your complaint is escalated and requires further investigation, your personal information is de-identified (made anonymous) and forwarded to Kimberly-Clark's manufacturing plants for the purposes of determining whether further inquiries into the manufacturing processes need to be conducted. If the complaint is of a particularly serious or urgent nature, then personal or health information about you may be provided to Kimberly-Clark's manufacturing plants or to external laboratories so that the issue may be analysed and resolved as quickly and effectively as possible. 

**Information collected through consumer promotions and market research**

Kimberly-Clark will use the personal information consumers' supply to us via on-pack promotional stickers, claim/entry forms, coupons, survey forms, questionnaires and through our websites for the purpose of providing you with incentives, prizes, samples and other promotional products, information and services. Any personal information you provide to us may be entered into a database, recorded in spreadsheets and kept in hard copy format. That information may be used for future promotional, marketing, market research, product development and publicity purposes. You may prevent such use of your personal information by opting-out at any time. 

We may share your personal information between different departments of Kimberly-Clark and with third parties such as fulfillment houses and advertising agencies who assist us with our promotional, marketing and research activities. We impose obligations on any external organisations with which we share your personal information to maintain the integrity and security of that information. 

**Can you access personal information that you have submitted to us?**

If your personal information changes (such as your address), or if you no longer wish us to keep your personal information on file, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove your records. We may charge you a small fee to cover any administrative costs that we may incur in providing personal information to you. If you believe for any reason that we are holding inaccurate or incomplete information about you, you may ask us to correct it. If you wish to access your personal information or if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or any complaint regarding treatment of your privacy by us, please contact: 

**The Privacy Officer**

Swati Chauhan   

Kimberly-Clark India Pvt. Ltd   
Address:Phoenix Market City, Art Guild House, A Wing, 3rd Floor, Office No- 9, Kamani, Mumbai,   
Maharashtra-400 070   
Phone: (022) 33220000 

**What if our privacy policy changes?**

We will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our websites so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose.
